(Amy:)and by extension, of course, yours.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, I'm-I'm still trying
(Leonard:)to work on the defecating
Clark Maxwell, so...
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, but a
grand unified theory,
(Sheldon:)insofar as it explains everything,
(Sheldon:)will ipso facto
explain neurobiology.
(Amy:)Yes, but if I'm successful,
(Amy:)I will be able to map and
reproduce your thought processes
(Amy:)in deriving a grand unified theory,
(Amy:)and therefore, subsume your
conclusions under my paradigm.
(Sheldon:)That's the rankest psychologism,
(Sheldon:)and was conclusively
revealed as hogwash
(Sheldon:)by Gottlob Frege in the 1890s!
(Amy:)We appear to have
reached an impasse.
(Sheldon:)I agree.
(Sheldon:)I move our relationship
terminate immediately.
(Amy:)Seconded.
(Sheldon:)There being no objections...
ALL: Uh-uh.
(Sheldon:)...the motion carries.
(Sheldon:)Good day, Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Amy:)Good day, Sheldon Cooper.